Finding aid to the Classes of 1951-1960 records CA.MS.01024
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1958 Records, 1954-2003; 3.292 linear feet (6 containers)
  The Class of 1958 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1958, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Speaker: John F. Kennedy, 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1954-1955 (Box 2212, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Prom, 1955 (Box 2212, Folder 5)
  - General, 1957 (Box 2212, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1954-1958; undated (Box 2212, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1957-1976; 2002 (Box 2212, Folder 9)
  - Officer Photographs, 1955 (Box 2212, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 2212, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2212, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1973-1978 (Box 2212, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2212, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1993-2003 (Box 2212, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Book (Box 2214.2)
  - Songs, 1957 (Box 2212, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who, 1954 (Box 2212, Folder 17)
  - Individuals A-Rh (Box 2213)
  - Individuals Ri-Z (Box 2214)
  - Hennessy, Kathleen Young (correspondence) (Box 2214.1)
  - Rittershofer, Anne (drawing) (Box 2214.3)
- Class of 1959 Records, 1955-2005; 2.625 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1959 was the eighty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1959 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1959, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1959 (Box 2215, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1955-1956 (Box 2215, Folder 2)
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 2215, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1955-1959 (Box 2215, Folder 4)
  - Class Letters, 1957-1982; 2002-2005 (Box 2215, Folder 5)
  - Organization, 1955-1957 (Box 2215, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2215, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2215, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2215, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2215, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2215, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Reunion Book, 1984 (Box 2215, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Alumnae Fund, 1990-1994 (Box 2215, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2215, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 2004 (Box 2215, Folder 15)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1957 (Box 2215, Folder 16)
  - Songs, 1959 (Box 2215, Folder 17)
  - Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 2215, Folder 18)
  - Who's Who, 1955 (Box 2215, Folder 19)
  - Individuals A-Bl (Box 2215)
  - Individuals Bo-R (Box 2216)
  - Individuals S-Z (Box 2217)
  - Chrisman, Mary (scrapbook) (Box 2217.1)
  - Hanley, Kathleen Adelia (memorabilia book) (Box 2217.1)
- Class of 1960 Records, 1956-2010; 3.083 linear feet (6 containers)
  The Class of 1960 was the eighty-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1960 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1960, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1960 (Box 2218, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, 1960 (Box 2218, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1960 (Box 2218, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1960 (Box 2218, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1956-1957 (Box 2218, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1956 (Box 2218, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Prom, 1957 (Box 2218, Folder 7)
  - General, 1958-1960 (Box 2218, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1956-1960 (Box 2218, Folder 9)
  - History, by Rita Seplowitz and Jane Yolen, 1960 (Box 2218, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1959 (Box 2218, Folder 11)
  - Class Letters, 1965-1976 (Box 2218, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters, 1992-2003 (Box 2218, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 2218, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2218, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2218, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Reunion Book, 1975 (Box 2218, Folder 17)
  - Reunions-Reunion Questionnaire Correspondence, 1975 (Box 2218, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1980-1995 (Box 2218, Folder 19)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1958 (Box 2218, Folder 20)
  - Who's Who, 1956 (Box 2218, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1961-1975 (Box 2219)
  - 15th Reunion Questionnaires, 1975 (Box 2219)
  - 15th Reunion Questionnaires-Final Report, 1975 (Box 2219.1, Folder 4)
  - 15th Reunion Questionnaires-Raw Data, 1975 (Box 2219.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1975-2010 (Box 2219.1)
  - Individuals A-M (Box 2220)
  - Individuals M-Z (Box 2221)
  - Unknown (book "The Saturday Evening Post"), 1960-06-04 (Box 1683.1)